foreign
folk welcome on into the channel my name
is Ashton wings and today we are going
to be doing something that I have not
really done here on the channel and
honestly I'm dooming it simply because I
am not sponsored with anybody yet I
wanted to go ahead and make a review
video for a product that maybe a lot of
you have heard about so
what we're talking about today are
sleeves right more specifically we are
talking
about Katana sleeves so I recently had a
small issue where I was at my LGS min
max games shout out to you guys you guys
are great I was over at min max games
and I bought a 100 pack of the crypt
dual matte sleeves from Dragon shield
now Dragon shield sleeves we can go
ahead and just talk about their stuff
right now this is Ember one of the Dual
matte sleeves and honestly I love how
these look I love how they feel they
Shuffle well personally I think they
Shuffle well
not to mention uh specifically the Dual
matte ones are black on the inside there
and then the actual color on the outside
so it helps kind of give everything a
flare you know now of course you Flesh
and Blood people are going to probably
yell at the fact that I have a Sigil of
Solace double sleeved but that's because
I have everything double sleeved so that
is just what I do but Dragon shield
essentially uh these are the these are
the sleeves I've been using for the
entirety of my time in Flesh and Blood
Dragon shield are the sleeves that I use
primarily in every TCG I've ever played
and again none of this is sponsored
right by Katana or Dragon shield I am
simply talking about the fact that
I like Dragon shield product but I had
an issue recently where buying that uh
the Crypt uh dual matte sleeves that are
just like these ones right with the the
dark interior and the uh the colorful
exterior I had bought a pack and they
were all slit at the bottom when you can
push this card through the bottom of the
sleeve every single one of them were
like that
and it was very unfortunate I was not
really
um you know I obviously was not happy
but I gotta be honest it is the first
time ever that I've ever had a problem
with Dragon shield sleeves ever so I'm
not going to count this as Dragon shield
as bad product so that this is not what
that is right there are people out there
who believe Dragon shield is bad product
and if that is your belief
understandable right I do really like
Dragon Shields product but I was given
an opportunity to try out Katana sleeves
because people there had said
specifically that Katana sleeves were
just better overall they are made in
Japan impeccable Clarity they have an
extra long lifespan and durability
perfect shuffling and acid free no PVC
so
of course you've got all the information
here in regards to Katana this comes in
the color there so uh I'm gonna go ahead
and open these up and we're going to see
how they feel coming in here I've heard
some uh I've heard some reserves about
Katana on whether or not they are
um
uh actually like
I'm gonna I'm gonna rip this thing open
so sorry
this was the the good side of having I'm
probably just opening this wrong
because I'm sure I am but
um the the positive side of being
uh Dragon shield sleeves were because
you were able to just like pop the
sucker open and you had a deck box so
well
a deck box but
uh this now is essentially just me
trying to open this thing here there we
go so you peel that back these sides
come up so I guess you could
theoretically put some stuff in here too
this opens up and here we go we have our
sleeves
so they come in two separate packs I'm
assuming this is in case you're running
like a 60 card deck or not
but these are our packs here
and we're gonna go ahead and check to
see how well they look so of course do
remember right this is the I've I've
used these a little bit so like you'll
see uh these have some love on them I
don't know if you're really going to be
able to see from that you see that that
waviness up at the top there obviously
there's been some use here it's been put
into deck boxes it's been taken out of
deck boxes uh when I put things into the
sleeves I push them down so of course
I'm causing that that oh that whole
issue there but
um you know that's on that's on me so
we're gonna go and take this out of here
and we're gonna see how well it looks
inside these new Katana sleeves I'm
curious
because like I said people have had
Reserves
about whether or not they should choose
Katana or they should choose uh Dragon
shield and the sole reason being is that
if you're double sleeving your deck
it looks better in Dragon shield sleeves
than it does in katana
so first impression it's got a nice
matte back more matte Believe It or Not
than the matte sleeves here at least
maybe that's just me they're all they're
almost identical
but I feel like this one kind of has a
a little bit more grit to it which is
nice and maybe not grit it's smooth it's
a smooth smooth sleeve so let's see
we'll go ahead and just open it up here
let's open from this side yep so we open
it up opens up nice
we're gonna go and put this guy in here
and we're gonna see how it looks
so this is our card
in there now
um I want to say that it looks pretty
good actually
it's a little
um too far up but maybe I'll push this
down and see if it changes anything here
that might be a little bit better yeah
there you go so believe it or not this
actually looks not too bad
let's go ahead and compare that to this
actually that's a bad example because
that's visual Solace is not there
compared to this
so you'll see the dimensions are
probably right around the same again
this is a Dragon shield this is a katana
sleeve
um so it's nice it feels good
and uh we're gonna we're gonna see uh
obviously like I said there's been a lot
of love with these so you can't really
give them any faults but so far these
feel sturdy they feel sturdy to hold
um it's it's not a bad sleeve I'm not
gonna lie this actually is just kind of
uh I'm no I'm no Aficionado on sleeves
but this does look pretty good so what
I'm going to do is I'm going to go ahead
and transfer my entire draw my deck into
these sleeves and we're gonna go ahead
and Shuffle it and see how well it
shuffles two hours later
all right thank goodness for editing
right so you guys don't have to watch
any of that so here we are the deck is
completely sleeved in here right looks
pretty clean except for this
this seems to be an issue and I think I
can just fix that with
[Music]
um
pushing the card down a little bit more
right because some of these
don't really sit in there too well
so you're going to want to make sure to
because there's not a lot of room at the
or there's yeah there's not a lot of
room at the top
so you're going to want to make sure
that if you are going to put cards in
that you really push them down
because they will kind of show through
almost and that's not
super great but that can be alleviated
through other means so not the end of
the world there
um but overall it looks pretty nice
um you know
pretty clean in there I would say
um obviously we can do the test right
you guys aren't going to be able to
really see but like
obviously they're fresh sleeves so
they're gonna do a little bit of
expanding
they're gonna do a little bit of of
movement
um
they are very very fragile
in their in their first opening uh as
most sleeves tend to be so just kind of
be cautious with them but I have 60
cards here I'm gonna go ahead and just
Shuffle
okay
so I know this isn't like almost
impossible for me to just
um
explain right through the feeling of
words but
uh
this actually does feel a lot better
uh it's a very smooth
uh Shuffle
there's
not a lot of resistance at all
um there normally really isn't but
there's not a lot of resistance
they Shuffle very very well
um nothing is getting caught on anything
sometimes you can hear a little bit of
crinkling and such from uh
from the Dragon shield ones uh at least
recently and it's not been too bad
but
these for sure
uh they pass the test they they feel
good I feel like obviously they're
they're fresh out the box so like this
is probably the best I'm ever gonna have
them in but
it's pretty great I'm not gonna lie the
the katana products not too shabby
This was
um how much does this go for
I don't actually know how much they go
for MSRP so check with your local game
store to see what these go for but uh
honestly if I were you I'd say give it a
shot there
they couldn't be more than Dragon shield
um I would say if there's one sleeve
that feels better than this
um you know personally that feels better
um I think the the one sleeve is the
slee the Dragon shield sleeves that have
the images on the back of them of like
the Flesh and Blood heroes or like even
the dragons and such those are really
really really nice they they feel good
they feel good to shuffle
um I've not had an issue with them I
don't know about any of the the slitting
through the bottom for that but what I
can say is that if you know I I don't I
don't feel comfortable taking those into
like a proquest because if you shuffle
your deck in a weird way and the image
ends up being upside down for any reason
right let's say you know in this case
right if your car if your TAP card is
upside down
like you don't really know until you
draw your card
and you're like oh well that's weird but
you don't really know but it's not until
you have a image on the card that if
that that ends up you know let's say
this is the image right if these are the
images and you're going through and you
go to draw a card
for some reason and this one
is an upside down image your opponent
can easily rule shark you for stacking
so I suggest that if you're going to go
into proquest which if I'm being honest
this video is probably going to be
posted
hopefully the day before proquest
um but if not uh it'll probably be the
day of the beginning of proquest so I
guess anywhere around the world I know
proquest is not just on Saturday the
14th that is just the beginning of it
but
um I highly suggest that if you are
going to pick up just matte sleeves with
just a color
uh katanas these are great these
actually do feel really really nice I
don't think I've ever gotten a a fresh
pack of sleeves
that have felt better right out of the
box now of course they do say a lot
about the longevity of the product they
say these are really really durable
they're durable card uh sleeves
so they will probably withstand the test
of time uh again if I were to give my
very very honest review
um if you're not double slaving your
cards not a probably one of the best
pickups you can get uh I personally am
double sleeving my cards just because
there are expensive cards in here but
these are double sleeved
um and you can kind of there's just not
a lot of room at the top there so you
really got to make sure that you're
pushing these cards down because if they
show at all again another rule shark
thing if at any point any of those cards
are showing are peeking through in any
way possible that your opponent is like
heavily looking for a way to card shark
you which you know unfortunately is the
case in most of these card games
um you are going to want to make sure
that your cards are just in a perfect
perfect situation so
I'm gonna be honest the katana sleeves
really impressed me I didn't think I I
honestly thought this would just be
another
I thought this would just be another
thing of sleeves you know like I was not
like
they they Shuffle in the hand well for
when I'm fidgeting
um maybe maybe not as well as dragon's
Shield but
they're they're not bad they're not bad
I like them a lot actually so I figure
we're gonna break them in tomorrow in an
Armory tonight at an Armory and we'll
kind of show you know maybe what what
that's going to be like right
um I still have a side deck to uh two
sleeves so I'll go ahead and do that uh
at the you know when this video is over
but I just wanted to give another shout
out to min max games for hooking me up
um you know they uh you know again this
is not a sponsored video for Katana but
I was recommended Katana over Dragon
shield uh specifically because there are
rumors that Dragon Shields quality has
gone down uh previously it was pretty
great but nowadays you're not finding as
great a quality in card sleeves so if
that is something that you wanted to try
out right there's there's no harm in
getting a pack of sleeves from a
different company you know unless you
are of course already Affiliated and
being sponsored by said company maybe
you're going to want to stick to Dragon
shield or Katana or Ultra Pro or
whatever part you're you're doing but
if I'm gonna be honest if you don't have
an affiliate to anything go get yourself
some Katana sleeves and then some Dragon
shield sleeves and you can just compare
the two right out the box and see which
ones work best for you
so thank you all so much for watching I
hope you guys enjoyed this uh this this
entire Katana sleeve review I uh this is
my first time doing a review for sleeves
and I feel like there's really not much
you can review
other than the color
the feel and the way they Shuffle and
how double sleeving fits in there so
double sleeving is probably like one of
the more like Advanced thing I wanted to
say Advanced it's really extra you it's
an extra thing that some people do for
cards if they're expensive and the
important thing is that if you if you
double sleeve one card in your deck you
have to double sleeve all of the cards
in your deck otherwise you could be
again card sharked for stacking so
make sure that if you are double
sleeving your deck you double sleeve the
whole thing if I'm being honest the
inner sleeves for this are Dragon shield
so the Inner Dragon shield sleeves uh
the clear ones the side loaders I use
those for the inner sleeves but these
Katana sleeves are probably what I'm
going to be using for the outers for
quite a little bit now these are nice so
Katana great job on making a pretty
awesome sleeve
um I hope it is crew to its word and
that it is very durable not that I'm
going to be like slamming cards down on
the table or whatever but you know I
plan to play a lot so I hope that they
hold up
so thank you all so much for watching so
let me know in the comments down below
whether or not your team Katana or team
Dragon shield I'd love to hear from all
of you I know there are some people who
are really loyal and dedicated and to be
honest I was pretty dedicated to Dragon
shield for a while but of course
you know you go ahead and uh and get
yourself some new sleeves and all of a
sudden your whole entire life has
changed so let me know what you guys
think about it and while you're down
there make sure to like the video and
subscribe to the channel as well if you
have not already uh maybe even let me
know what you'd like me to review next
for you guys if you had any uh you know
ideas about maybe like deck boxes or
deck binders or so on so forth I'd love
to kind of review them and go over what
I use over you know some other people
what they might use too so thank you
again so much I do truly appreciate your
support and I will see you all very soon
nerd out
[Music]